1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Records 6347
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV. Campaigns and Organizations, 1969-2020; 1948-2020
  - Final Offer on RWDSU Mott's Strike, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Internal Communications on RWDSU Mott's Strike, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Press Releases on RWDSU Mott's Strike, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - News Coverage of RWDSU Mott's Strike, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Agreements between Strong Memorial Hospital, University of Rochester Medical Center and 1199 SEIU (4 agreements), 2010-2020 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    2010-2012; 2012-2014; 2014-2017; 2017-2020
  - 1199 SEIU - CBA, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Empire Justice Center: Wage Theft Project, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Occupy Rochester Internal Communications, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Occupy Rochester Posters and Press Releases, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - The Occupy Movement in Other Cities, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - We Are One Rochester Network, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - We Are One Coalition Meeting Notes, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - "Restore the Promise" Campaign (We Are One), 2011 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Campaign Against Millionaire Tax Cuts (We Are One), 2011 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Rochester-Genesee Valley Area Labor Federation (RGVALF) Materials, 2011-2012 (Box 11, Folder 24-26)
  - News Articles on Occupy Rochester, 2011-2012 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Arc of Monroe, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Contains materials relating to the lost unionization vote.
  - 1199 SEIU - Nursing Center, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Straus/Lexington Nursing Home
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital Negotiations, 2012 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Election Forms/Flyers, 2012-2013 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Hospital Records, 2012-2016 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Includes material related to University of Rochester, 1199SEIU election, and "We Are One" movement.
  - Rochester Labor Council Materials, 2013-2015 (Box 11, Folder 19-23)
  - Draft Applications for Rochester Workers' Center, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Application for Rochester Workers' Center (Metro Justice), 2014 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Rochester Genesee Valley Area, Labor Federation, AFL-CIO, 2014 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - NYCLU Campaign Finance Center, 2014 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - "POWER" Steering Committee Meetings, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Rochester/Genesee Valley Labor Materials, 2014-2016 (Box 11, Folder 29-31)
  - Anthony Jordan Health Center, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Rochester Labor Council 2016 Election, 2015-2016 (Box 11, Folder 2-6)
  - NYCLU Statewide Presence Center, 2015-2016 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital Patent Care Techs, 2016 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Collective bargaining agreement between Corning Hospital and the 1199SEIU, 2016-2018 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Poverty/Jobs Task Force Meeting (Roc/ACTS), 2017 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - NYS Fight for Minimum Wage, 2017-2019 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Elder Justice Committee (Metro Justice), 2018 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Rochester Low Wage Worker Roundtable, 2018 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Home Health Care, 2018 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Nazaeth Adjunct Faculty Drive, 2018 (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Second Mayoral Inauguration of Lovely Warren, 2018 (Box 33, Folder 84)
  - 1199 SEIU 30th Anniversary Celebration, 2019 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Sarah Clark - NYS Senate, 2020 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - 2020 Democratic Primary Election (Box 33, Folder 85)
  - 1199 Political Action, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - 1199 Rochester MLK Celebration (URMC), Undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 1199-SEIU Merger, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Anthony Reed, Undated (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Association for union democracy, Undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Bella Abzug, Undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Bread & Roses Project, Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Bread and Roses Project, Undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Campus Times, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Campus Times Vol. 18; no. 33-37, Undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Dale Rath, Undated (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - District 1199 - Wisconsin, Undated (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
  - E. Gilman - Health & Safety Grant Application, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Anthony Jordan Health Center
  - Gary Proud, Undated (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Information on "POWER" Community Coalition, Undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - John Perry, Undated (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Louise Slaughter, Undated (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Lovely Warren, Undated (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Maxine Childress Brown, Undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Memorial Art Gallery of the University of Rochester, Undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Memorial Art Gallery of the University of Rochester, Undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Nat'l. Caucus of Labor Committees / US Labor Party, Undated (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - NYS Assembly - Virgilio, Undated (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - NYSCOSH, Undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Material relating to involvement in ROCOSH.
  - Politicians - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Registering to Vote Informations Pamphlets, Undated (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - RLC Constitution, Projects and Allies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Rochester Council on Occupational Safety & Health (ROCOSH), Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Rochester Peace P.A.C., Undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - SEIU/1199 Unity is Strength, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Solidarity Day Information, Undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Union Busters - Corning Hospital, Corning, NY, Undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital Flyers, Undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital Undated Documents (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Series V. News Clippings and Union Handouts, 1968-2019; 1949-2019
  Includes all newspaper clippings (separated out mostly by year), as well as recurring documents like magazines, and union advertising tools like handouts or their own papers/magazines. Organized chronologically.
  - Agreement between The New York Central Railroad Company, The Grand Central Terminal and The Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Constitution of the Grand Lodge - Statutes for the Government of Lodges and Protective Laws of the Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employes (2 constitutions), 1955-1959 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    1955, 1959
  - SDS New Left Notes, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Dulocratic Review, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Thrust, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Currents, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees - US Labor Party, 1969-1978 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Gargoyle, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - News Clippings, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Alumni News, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Currents, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Rochester Review, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York and Local 1199, 1970-1972 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Illyria, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Forum, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Currents, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - New Solidarity, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1973-1981 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Health Care System, 1973-2019 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Dollars & Sense (Nov.-Dec.), 1974 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - The Campaigner (Nov-Dec), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Nov.-Dec.), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - History & Historians, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Anti-Management Handouts, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 68)
  - 1199SEIU Benefits Handouts, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 69)
  - Workers' Rights Handouts, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 70)
  - Genesee Co-Op, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee - New American Movement, 1974-1982 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - American Civil Liberties Union ACLU, 1974-2018 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Industrial Workers of the World (IWW), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1975 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Dec.), 1975 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - United Farmworkers (UFW) AFL-CIO, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Catholicism Related Handouts, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 71)
  - Agreement between Local No. 222, United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America and American Optical Scientific Instrument Division Buffalo Plant, 1975-1978 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - United Auto Workers (UAW), 1975-1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1975-1988 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - United Food & Commercial Workers (UFCW), 1975-1988 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1976 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Dec.), 1976 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - 1199 News, 1976-1978 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - 1199 Newsletter, 1976-1981 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - United Mineworkers of America, 1976-1989 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Catholic Worker Organization, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1977 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Dec.), 1977 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Oct.), 1977 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - Elections, 1977-1982 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - AFL-CIO Memos and Publications, 1977-1995 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO, 1977-2019 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Management Performance, Inc., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - International Association of Machinists, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Progressive Alliance, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Dec.), 1978 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - 1199 News, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - 1199 "These Are the Days" Calendar, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - OFC & Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Rebel Worker Organization, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Printing Trades - International Typographical Union; Graphic Arts International Union, 1978-1981 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Labor Today, 1978-1982 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Rochester Patriot Newspaper, 1978-1982 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - SEIU Local #200 (New York State), 1978-1983 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Communications Workers of America (CWA), 1978-1985 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Democratic Party, 1978-2011 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Unions & Professionals, 1978-2012 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 1199 News, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Rochester Teachers Association (NYSUT), 1979 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Arts Council of Rochester, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Rochester Safe Energy Alliance, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1979 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Feb.-Dec.), 1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - NYS United Teachers, AFT, AFL-CIO, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - American Nurses Association - Economics & General Welfare Dept., 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers - AFL-CIO, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - San Mateo County, CA AFL-CIO, 1979-1984 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - BFLO & WNY Hospital & Nursing Home Workers Council AFL-CIO, 1979-1991 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Voter Registration, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Dec.), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - League of Registered Nurses Handouts, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 72)
  - Hotel, Restaurant Union, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - SEIU Service Employees International Union, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Daycare, 1980-1982 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Center for Youth Services, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Urban League of Rochester, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - C.L.U.W. - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1980-1984 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU), 1980-1985 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - United States Gout, 1980-1986 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - International Union of Electrical Workers (IUE), 1980-1987 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - 1199 News, 1980-1995 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Handouts Using Endorsements for 1199, 1980-2008 (Box 33, Folder 73)
  - AFSCME (including CSEA), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - NYS Nurses Association (NYSNA), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Public Employee Fed (PEF) SEIU-NYSUT, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Working Women (National Association of Office Workers) SEIU, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - UAW = District 65 - Cornell Employees, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - American for Democratic Action, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1199 News Magazine (July-Dec.), 1981 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - Professional Air Traffic Controllers Organization (PATCO), 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Education, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Environmental Issues, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Screen Actors Guild, 1981-1985 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Sierra Club, 1981-1985 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Sierra Club - NYS - Atlantic Chapter, 1981-1985 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Broome Co. Community - Labor Coalition, 1981-1986 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Newspapers and Meeting Notes, 1981-2014 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Buffalo AFL-CIO Council, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Legislative Bulletin & Memos, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - United Way of Rochester, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Dec.), 1982 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - White Collar Report (Bureau of Nat. Affairs), 1982-1985 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Sierra Club - Rochester, 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Sierra Club, 1982-1993 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - 1199 Newsletter, 1982-1999 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - District 1199 News, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Articles, Correspondence - Misc. Sources, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - National Education Association (NEA), 1983 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Dec.), 1983 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - News Clippings, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - 1199's Tenth Birthday Publication, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - CWA #1168 Nurses United, 1983-1987 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - AFL-CIO Foreign Policy, 1983-1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Rochester Labor Calendar, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Bakery, Confectionary & Tobacco Workers International Union, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1984 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Medicare Programs, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Dec.), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - News Clippings, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - International Longshore & Warehouse Union (ILWU), 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Interface, 1984-1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Medicaid Programs, 1984-2005 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1985 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Dec.), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - UAW Amino Handouts, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - George Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Anti-Apartheid Movement, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1986 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Dec.), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - "The Organizer" Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - "Health Sector Trends" Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Eastman Kodak Co., 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Economic Notes - Labor Research Assoc., 1986-1992 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Health Care, 1986-2000 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Corporate Campaign - Legal Issues, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Dec.), 1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - News Clippings, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - CWA Publications, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Newspaper Guild, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Corporate Campaign, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Unions and Nurses, 1987-1993 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1988 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Democratic Socialists of America, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.-Aug.), 1988 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - 1199 News Magazine (Jan.), 1988 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - 1199 Health & Safety, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1989 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - News Clippings - Misc. Sources, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - LRA'a Economic Notes, 1990-1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1991 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - News Clippings, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1992 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - Celebrating the Life of Leon Davis, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1993 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - 1199 Rochester SEIU In The News, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - News Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Economic Notes (LRA), 1995-1998 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Remarks and Published Articles by Bruce Popper, 1995-2018 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1996 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - SEIU - Local 1199 Upstate, 1996-2001 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Dollars & Sense (Mar.-Dec.), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Book Lists, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - 1998 Rolex Awards for Enterprise Application (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1998 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 1999 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - News Clippings, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - SEIU in the news, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1199 Upstate - SEIU, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1199 Upstate The News, 1999-2001 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - SEIU - Special Editions (In the News), 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Best of SEIU 1199 In The News, 1999-2002 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - SEIU in the news Spring/Summer 2000 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - SEIU in the news - Fall 2000 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Dec.), 2000 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - SEIU 1199 Upstate In The News, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 61)
  - Best of SEIU - 1199 Upstate in the news, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SEIU 1199Upstate Communications Report, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - News Clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - 1199 Upstate Annual Report, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - SEIU in the news March-May, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - SEIU in the news October - November, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - SEIU in the news June - September (Copy 1), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - SEIU in the news June - September (Copy 2), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - SEIU in the news December - February, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - SEIU Testimony, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - America @ Work, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Dollars & Sense (Jan.-Aug.), 2001 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Bread and Roses Film, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - SEIU "Action" Magazine, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - SEIU 1199Upstate In The News, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 63)
  - News Clips, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Unit Newsletters/Bulletins, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - SEIU in the news December - February, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Press Releases, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - News Clips, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Unit Newsletters, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - News Clips, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Unit Newsletters, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Press Releases, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - News Clips, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Unit Newsletters, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Unit Newsletters, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - News Clips, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - News Clips, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - News Clips, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - SEIU in the news February - April, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - SEIU in the news April - June, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SEIU in the news June - August, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "Celebrate Moe!" Magazine, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 64)
  - Local 1199 Upstate News, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 1199 SEIU Bi-Weekly Bulletin, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Local 1199 Upstate News, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 65)
  - Press Releases, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - News Clippings, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Chapter Newsletters, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Press Releases - 1199 SEIU, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - News Clips, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chapter Newsletter - Hospitals, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1199SEIU "Delegates" Magazine, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 66)
  - NYCLU Broadway Stands for Freedom, 2003-2018 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 2003-2020 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - News Clippings, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - News Clippings, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - Biographies, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 77)
  - News Clippings, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 78)
  - News Clippings, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 79)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2009-2014 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU), 2009-2016 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - News Clippings, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 80)
  - News Clippings, 2011 (Box 32, Folder 81)
  - News Clippings, 2012 (Box 32, Folder 82)
  - NYCLU Economic Rts. Committee, 2012-2016 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - News Clippings, 2013 (Box 32, Folder 83)
  - News Clippings, 2014 (Box 32, Folder 84)
  - "Rochester: For Your Benefit" Magazine, 2014-2016 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Popper: "Longtime Activist Labors For Cause" Profile, 2015 (Box 32, Folder 85)
  - News Clippings, 2016 (Box 32, Folder 86)
  - 1199-SEIU Materials, 2016-2017 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union (NYCLU), 2017-2020 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - News Clippings, 2018 (Box 32, Folder 87)
  - Boxes are charged with breaking the law in over 40% of union campaign, 2019 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Unprecedented: The Trump NLRB's attack on workers' rights, 2019 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Federal Judge issues restraining order on aspects of NYS farmworkers fair labor law, 2019 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - News Clippings, 2019 (Box 32, Folder 88)
  - "Organizing Defines 1199" Article, Undated (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - 1199 Guild Division, Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - 1199 League of R.N.'s, Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 1199 Rochester Reading List (Interns), Undated (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - 1199 Southern States, Undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Activist, Undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - AFL CIO News, Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Amalgamated Clothing & Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) AFL-CIO, Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union, Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - American Friends Service Committee, Undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Because There is No Radio Free America, Undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Buffalo Sun, Undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Committee of Interns & Residents (CIR), Undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Corporate Campaign, Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Corporate Campaign, Undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Articles - Misc. Sources, Undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Dispatcher, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - District 1199 - New England, Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - District 1199 - West VA - Kentucky - Ohio, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - District 1199 - Wisconsin, Undated (Box 14, Folder 30)